CLARENCE PHILLIPS

ELECTRICIAN \$\square\$ 951-331-6919

• DETAILS •

951-331-6919 lonelyparkbench@gmail.com

o SKILLS o

Customer Service

Creativity

Teamwork

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Multitask

Adaptability

Effective Time Management

Leadership Skills

Fast Learner

Critical thinking and problem solving

Communication Skills

Strategic Planning

PROFILE

Top performing Commercial Electrician of 5 years, empowered to achieve high standards.

Awarded by Alco Building Solutions, Electrician of the 2019 year.

Excellent time management, planning and problem solving skill's to complete tasks in a swift well executed manner.

10 years experience operating heavy equipment, Backhoe's, Skid-steer's, Forklift's, Scissor Lift's, Boom Lift's, Asphalt roller's.

Specialty-Installing EV charger's, Running Conduit.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Eclectrician at Alco Building Solutions

December 2018 — Present

Electrician at D & D Electric

November 2017 — December 2018

Electrician at Sierra West Electric

February 2017 — November 2017

Busser at Bj's Brewhouse

October 2015 — February 2017

Kitchen Manager at Chipotle

June 2014 — October 2015

Drive Thru at Mcdonalds

September 2013 — June 2014

EDUCATION

High School Diploma, Hamilton High

¶ REFERENCES

Joeseph Hilke from Alco Bulding Solutions

626-315-5471

Jaden Weir from D & D Electric

951-557-0399

Chris Luong from Alco Building Solutions

626-436-4082